<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localization xmlns="http://schemas.ximeta.com/meta/loc/2006">
  <string id="COND_X64_IS_NOT_SUPPORTED">
    <base>This setup package is for 32-bit version of Windows. Please install the 64-bit version of this software.</base>
    <translation>이 설치 프로그램은 32비트 버전의 Windows용입니다. 64비트 설치 프로그램으로 설치해 주세요,</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="COND_REQUIRE_WIN2000">
    <base>[ProductName] requires that your computer is running Windows 2000, Windows XP or Windows 2003 Server.</base>
    <translation>[ProductName] 은 Windows 2000, XP, 2003 서버에 설치할 수 있습니다.</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="COND_NOT_PRIVILEGED">
    <base>You do not have sufficient privileges to complete this installation. Log on as an administrator and then retry this installation.</base>
    <translation>설치할 권한이 없습니다. 관리자로 로그온 후 재시도 해 주세요.</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="ProductName64Suffix">
    <base> (64-bit Windows)</base>
    <translation>-</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="Text.SetupVersion">
    <base>[NdasSetupVersion]</base>
    <translation>-</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="ReadyToInstall.NoticeText2">
    <base>It is recommended that this product is used in 100Mbps wired LAN or 802.11g/a wireless LAN environment.</base>
    <translation>이 제품은 100Mbps 유선 랜이나 802.11g/a 무선 랜 환경에 적합합니다.</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="ReadyToInstall.NoticeText1">
    <base>If you are using this product in a wired 10Mbps LAN or wireless 802.11b LAN environment, there is a possiblity of data transmit error or unstable connection.</base>
    <translation>무선 10Mbps 랜이나 무선 802.11b 환경에서 사용할 경우 데이터 전송 에러 혹은 불안정한 접속 현상이 있을 수 있습니다.</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="ReadyToInstall.NoticeGroupBox">
    <base>Notice</base>
    <translation>주의</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="SFWarning.SFWarnCheck">
    <base>I &amp;acknowledge this warning message.</base>
    <translation>경고 내용을 알고 있습니다.(&amp;A)</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="SFWarning.DlgDesc">
    <base>Setup detected a software.</base>
    <translation>설치 프로그램이 소프트웨어를 찾았습니다.</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="SFWarning.DlgTitle">
    <base>{&amp;MSSansBold8}Compatibility Warning</base>
    <translation>{&amp;MSSansBold8}호환성 경고</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="SFWarning.MemoLine1">
    <base>{&amp;Arial8BoldBlue}Setup has found that StarForce Copy Protection software is installed in your system. Some old versions of this software may cause a system crash for using thirdy party storage device drivers.</base>
    <translation>{&amp;Arial8BoldBlue}설치 프로그램이 시스템에 설치된 StarForce 복제 방지 소프트웨어를 찾았습니다. 몇 이전 버전의 소프트웨어는 다른 저장 장치 드라이버와 시스템 충돌을 일으킬 수 있습니다. </translation>
  </string>
  <string id="SFWarning.MemoLine2">
    <base>It is highly recommended to update the StarForce Copy Protection software before proceeding the installation. Check the web site of the Protection Technology (http://www.star-force.com) for the updates.</base>
    <translation>설치를 진행하기 전 StarForce 복제 방지 소프트웨어를 업데이트 하세요. Protection Technology 웹 사이트를 찹조하세요 (http://www.star-force.com).</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="UpgradeConfirm.DlgDesc">
    <base>Setup has found a previous version of the software.</base>
    <translation>이전 소프트웨어를 찾았습니다.</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="UpgradeConfirm.DlgTitle">
    <base>{&amp;MSSansBold8}Upgrade Confirmation</base>
    <translation>{&amp;MSSansBold8}업그레이드 확인</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="UpgradeConfirm.MemoLine1">
    <base>Setup has found a previous version of the software and will perform an upgrade. During an upgrade, you may have to reboot the system twice.</base>
    <translation>설치 프로그램이 이전 버전의 소프트웨어를 찾아 업그레이드를 수행하려고 합니다. 업그레이드 중에는 시스템을 두 번 리부팅 하여야 할 수 있습니다.</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="UpgradeConfirm.MemoLine2">
    <base>To ensure proper operation, please do not interrupt the system reboot and follow the instructions until the setup is completed.</base>
    <translation>정상적인 장동을 위해 시스템 리부팅을 방해하지 말고 설치가 완료될 때 까지 지시에 따라주세요. </translation>
  </string>
  <string id="UpgradeConfirm.MemoLine3">
    <base>Click Next to continue installation.</base>
    <translation>다음을 눌러 설치를 진행해 주세요.</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="Error.25900">
    <base>Newer version of the software is already installed. If you have to downgrade the software, uninstall the higher version software first.</base>
    <translation>이 소프트웨어의 새 버전이 이미 설치되어 있습니다. 다운그레이드하려면 우선 상위 버전의 소프트웨어를 삭제해 주세요.</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="Error.27500">
    <base>This setup requires Internet Information Server 4.0 or higher for configuring IIS Virtual Roots. Please make sure that you have IIS 4.0 or higher.</base>
    <translation>이 설치 프로그램은 Internet Information Server Virtual Roots 설정을 위해 IIS 4.0 이상이 설치되어야 합니다. IIS 4.0 이상이 설치되어 있는지 확인해 주세요.</translation>
  </string>
  <string id="Error.27501">
    <base>This setup requires Administrator privileges for configuring IIS Virtual Roots.</base>
    <translation>이 설치 프로그램이 IIS Virtual Roots를 설정하기 위해 관리자 권한이 필요합니다.</translation>
  </string>
</localization>